How in the world did this ever happen?
Am I dying tomorrow or something?
Cut it out.
You know, I was wondering last night, does your dad call you cute nicknames or anything?
He doesn't do it that often anymore, but obvious stuff like Kyo.
What about your friends?
Ichikawa, or maybe just Ichi?
Then how about I call you Kyo-Taro?
What do you think?
Yup, I'm definitely a dead man.
I'll call you later!
Sure.
Yamada's off to Hiroshima today for one of her shoots.
Oh...
Forgot to wish her good luck.
As for me...
Yurin's caught in a big scandal! She was out all night!
Well, I still believe her!
She said it was just a good friend of hers and all they did was play games all night like friends do!
Huh. Like that's believable.
Totally. Can't call yourself an otaku if you don't believe the idols you worship.
Right? Only true-
Why did those words hit so hard?
Cherry blossom viewing though, huh?
I'd heard tales, but never thought it was real. Definitely didn't imagine I'd find myself joining.
Well, if it isn't easy.
I totally knew it. I swore I recognized that obnoxious voice of yours.
Hey! Um, what are you doing here anyway?
Us guys were busy talking about the economy and stuff.
More like gossiping about Yurin's little scandal, I bet.
Let them kiss. Let them sleep over.
So long as they're dating.
Even I'd be angry if they spent the night and weren't even going out together.
Talk about scandalous and upsetting her fans. Right? Know what I mean?
Think about it. Yamada spent the night at the house of a guy she isn't even dating.
That's the hard and honest truth. She might not be as famous as Yurin, but even still...
I assume you know how your relationship will hinder her performance.
We might have just made a big mistake.
Hey, let's send a pic to Yamada. Say cheese!
Hmm?
Wait!
Hey, uh, speaking of, why isn't she with you?
She starts filming in Hiroshima tomorrow.
He decided to head there a day early.
Yeah, and she's playing Ken Kataoka's daughter.
For real? No way!
She gets more amazing every day, doesn't she?
Mm-hmm.
Although, she's still the same Yamada. She'll never change up how she is.
True dat.
Hardly believed my eyes the other day.
Down some ramen and eat me two burgers.
I wish she would talk about me like that.
Yeah.
Maybe she won't change.
But...
It's such a fancy hotel!
Want me to give you a tour?
Some things have to...
Yamada...
Huh?
Oh, hold on, okay?
Oh, hey, Mom.
Listen, Anna.
Can we talk?
Huh?
And just like that, the day went by with nothing said.
So beautiful.
Huh?
Don't you think so?
What?
Oh, thank you very much.
I meant the view.
Oh.
Ken Kataoka!
Now on set!
Mm-hmm.
It's a pleasure to work with you!
Just relax, you'll do fine.
Alright.
All I can do is send generic, unhelpful messages.
Her mom might be mad at her for staying the night.
She's not just some ordinary junior high kid.
I need to be more conscious of that fact.
Wait a minute, is this?
No way!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I knew it!
What were you thinking, Yamada?
This is how problems start!
Look, see? There's always someone!
These comments reek of otaku-ness, all from the same account, too.
Pig man? Hmm...
Fan of ramen and idols.
Basically a normal old dude.
This guy has lost it!
This reason for living?
Another scandal!
What's this guy posting about?
You don't get to decide that!
What's pig man's deal?
There are people out there who are gonna love making a huge deal out of this!
He's getting lots of engagement.
This gives me no pleasure, but...
That should do it!
Now, quit making me do this embarrassing stuff, otaku man!
Hm?
Seriously?! He blocked me?!
What does it matter to you, anyway?!
Quit acting like a real dad only when it suits you!
And cut!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
I didn't mean to start crying yet!
No, that was good! Just like that, right?
No, we cut before they fell.
So, you're with Techan's agency, aren't you?
Oh, I am!
That was good!
I felt you played the scene more anxious than afraid.
Teenagers are really something. Just gotta love them, don't ya?
I also got to watch the rest of the shoot after that, too!
Ken Kataoka really is an amazing actor!
But he was complimenting you, so maybe you're the one who's amazing!
No, I'm really not.
I'm really not.
In that scene...
I didn't get why I started crying like that.
That moment, though...
I felt like maybe...
I started to understand you a bit more.
I was feeling frustrated and anxious...
But I think Mr. Kataoka saw right through me!
I'm really glad that I got to stay over the other night
and talk with you like that.
My mom was a little mad, though.
So you did get in trouble then?
Yeah.
I'm not gonna tell you not to lie.
That's pointless.
Because I know I lied to my own mother plenty of times.
But I really want to be here for you during all your phases of life.
So don't forget that, alright?
Thanks, Yamada!
What?
That's my line!
Oh, is it really?
Thank goodness.
None of this has been for nothing.
Not our sleepover.
Not this anxiety.
Her mom is there with her, so I doubt there will be any problem with the shoot.
The real problem is, if she keeps uploading stuff like this, the otaku are gonna have a field day!
Hey!
Can I show this cute picture of me and Ana off to my friends?
What?
This adorable one here!
You absolutely cannot!
Delete that right now!
Go microwave your phone!
Hey!
What?
This adorable one here!
You absolutely cannot!
Delete that right now!
Go microwave your phone!
Hey!
Uhh!
Uh…
Hang on!
What's this... heavy burden on my chest?
I know.
I'm not trying to...
I just, I know exactly how this guy feels.
Adoration turned to abhorrence.
Can you see it?
Think that's Shikoku over there?
Beats me.
Maybe it's the Shimanami Kaido?
How can you literally be there and not know?
Listen though, you're alone right now, right?
Yeah, my mom had to make a work call.
So we can talk about anything you want.
That's not why I asked.
Mike, come on a little heavy,
telling her there's a rabid fan nearby.
Look, it's nothing.
Just be careful about what's behind you.
Oh, did you see it too?
Huh?
Virgo is at the bottom of the horoscope.
I always ignore all the bad readings, don't you know?
What's with the accent?
Girls with accents are so cute, right?
Huh?
Yamada?
Yamada!
This can't be happening.
It's probably fine.
Gotta be.
No problem.
Nope.
Something's definitely wrong here, right?
Go for it.
Relax for a minute.
No.
I don't even care if they hate me for it.
Huh?
Um, f-fancy bumping into you here.
I was just stepping out of the rain.
I just need to know that she's okay.
It's 11 o'clock.
Seeing her dad like this should tell me if she's-
You look pretty cold, you okay?
Huh?
You're freezing.
Come in.
Huh?
Oh, delicious.
That's a professional cook for you.
Michelle- It's late, call your parents.
What?
Michelle- Kids shouldn't stay out at people's houses this late.
Jessica- Crap, is he mad?
Now that I think about it, I'm acting like a real creep right now.
Who am I to tell Pigman off?
Yeah, Ana?
Right now?
What? A message?
Slow down. Where?
Here, you know this place?
Huh? That's...
On the water.
Wants me to tell the people here she can't respond.
Oh, I'll try calling her back then.
Th-that's my house.
Huh?
That's my house. Right there.
I see.
That's so?
Huh?
Oh, uh...
Come on now, Yuki. Miss me already, do you?
Um, I'm, uh...
What? Who is this?
Sorry, this is Ichikawa, ma'am. Ichikawa.
Huh? Ichikawa?
Kotaro!
Oh my gosh, listen!
My mom showed up and when I turned around and saw her, I dropped my phone in the water!
It's gone for good!
I knew you'd be worried, so I was writing letters to you so you knew I was okay!
Calm down. Take a deep breath.
Wait, but why are you at my place?
Um...
That's actually a good question.
You know, you can restore all your data from the cloud.
Hey!
Um...
Huh?
Mom...
Well, you see...
I, um...
There's something...
I need to tell you.
I like Ana!
And not in some half-hearted way.
So I'm really sorry about the whole sleepover thing.
Hmm.
My friend code.
Let's game sometime.
Huh?
And so...
Our tumultuous spring break came to an end.
Come on, there's more to Tokyo than just ramen!
Huh?
Oh, right!
Let me check that other account I made.
Huh?
That's right!
They've posted about this before!
How could I forget?
This is how it always is!
The crazy ones strike when you least expect it!
Yamada!
Huh?
Kyo!
Friend of yours?
Oh!
He's, um…
Ooh, that's right.
You're the one from before.
Oh!
I...
This girl...
She was at that photo shoot.
She's the one Yamada looks up to.
Mm-hmm.
But where's Pigman?
We just bumped into each other here.
I want to ask her to go somewhere else, but I can't with this girl here!
Yamada!
Amada, is it okay if I join you?
Sure.
Come on in.
Welcome.
Hey, why don't you take this seat here, Ana?
Thanks, this is perfect.
Huh?
Hmm?
Hey, Ana.
No way.
How is Onomichi?
A famous model would never...
I grew up there, don't you know?
You're Pigman.
Uh, way to make it obvious.
Here you are.
But I ordered a small with no extra toppings, sir.
And that's what I gave you.
Oh, crap.
I've read about Ramen Rose somewhere.
It's one of those places where they serve customers in groups of five at a time.
Anyone who holds up the next group earns the resentment of the whole staff.
Shoot, this isn't the sort of place you just stroll into.
Oh, that was fast!
So, by the way...
I'm Thanatos.
I'm a fan of Yamada.
Of Ana Akino, too.
Who wouldn't be?
She's amazing.
So cute, so cool, so calm and grown up.
She's perfect.
This is expected.
Yamada's bound to have even more obsessed fans as she gets more famous.
But...
I know Yamada.
The one who isn't perfect.
The real Ana Yamada.
Sorry, but I win.
Hold up.
Put your bow up top.
That was long.
Wait, did you happen to get taller since I last saw you?
Okay, Grandma.
I'm just wearing high heels.
Ichikoa, your shoes.
I can explain.
Did you rush out the door to get here?
What?
Anna, you've never made that face.
Oh, wow, that's adorbs.
I just wanted to...
Actually, I've always looked up to you, Nico,
and I just want you to know you're just the coolest person there is in the industry.
Thank you.
I hope we can hang out again soon.
No thanks.
I prefer to keep a healthy distance from my idols.
True otaku.
But as long as the feeling's mutual...
See ya.
Oh, wait.
You can't go posting Yamada's personal info willy-nilly online.
Um, what are you talking about?
Hmm?
What is happening?
I just exchanged contact info with the famous model.
Oh.
I'm sorry about my phone.
You must have been worried.
No.
I'm the one who imagined terrible things happening.
But you know...
Hmm?
There are bad people out there who want nothing more than to see famous faces fall.
So then, be a little more careful about the pictures you post.
And make sure to keep some distance in crowded spaces like this.
Right.
I don't want you to worry anymore.
From now on, I want to be more adult-like.
That's right.
Appropriate distance.
Wants to be adult?
Interesting choice.
Shut up!
I want to grow up!
I want to you.
I want to know all of you.
I'm sorry.
Woman.
You'll see me.
You're left.
I want to know all those Philly PS comes.
You beat me!
What?
I love it.
I love you.
You're my Hydra Prince.
You're my...
You're myct.
hurts.
I love you.
You're my بد.
You're my best.